freddieawards.com 2013-05-28

# Freddie Awards

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is offered by the Freddie Awards as an extension of our commitment to combine a quality event, personal service, and the integrity in serving as the voice of the frequent flyer. This Privacy Policy covers the Freddie Awards and any associated content including RSS feeds, emails, email newsletters, surveys, member comments, and other applications.

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the Freddie Awards. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of sponsors/partners that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We only collect information from you when you fill out a form to receive our newsletter updates. This is a double opt-in procedure managed by our email client which means others are not able to sign up people who did not give permission to be added to the list. This process is managed by MailChimp, one of the largest and most respected email management companies in the world. Outside of your voluntarily action to receive the newsletter updates, you remain totally anonymously to us.

### WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Broadly speaking, any of the information we collect from you is used in the following way:

  * To send periodic emails: the email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your interest in the results of the Freddie Awards (winners), the conversations/dialogues about the Freddie Awards on other partner websites or information about a winner of prizes donated by some of our sponsors/partners.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of physical, electronic, and administrative security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information (email address) when you voluntarily add yourself to our mail list.

### HOW DO WE SECURE YOUR INFORMATION?

We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of the information. Again we use a recognized leading email company to mange your information.

### DO WE USE COOKIES?

Yes, the Freddie Awards utilizes standard technologies called ?cookies? and "log files" to collect information about how the Freddie Awards is used. Cookies are very small text files saved to your computer used to track your navigation around the Freddie Awards. This cookie is not identifiable other than by the website server, and does not store any information which could disclose personal information about you. Log files are merely a record of this information. Other information gathered may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent on the Freddie Awards, the websites visited just before and just after the Freddie Awards, what type of web browser (Internet Explorer, Chrome, Firefox, etc.) you are using, and your Internet Protocol (?IP?) address. Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous as part of an overall analytics review. If you do not wish to transmit ?cookie? information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the ?Help? section of your personal browser to correctly do so.

### DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO ADVERTISERS OR OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to advertisers, sponsors, partners or outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our site such as our email list manager, so long as these outside parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. Our email list is not shared, even with sponsors or partners.

### THIRD PARTY LINKS

We may include or offer third party products or services on our site such as our sponsors and partners via links to their properties. These third party websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Freddie Awards and welcome any feedback about these other websites.

### ANYTHING ELSE?

There may be times when we may ask you to provide relevant data regarding your preferences and demographics information to answer survey questions. As in other instances, we will use this information in a non-personally identifiable manner.

### WHAT ABOUT MY EMAIL ADDRESS?

Your email privacy is absolutely our top priority, and we will never, ever, sell that information to anyone. We may however, use your email address to send the following types of messages to you:

  * information and updates pertaining to your interest in the results of the Freddie Awards (winners).
  * information about the start and finish of the Freddie Awards voting periods.
  * information relevant to conversations/dialogues about the Freddie Awards voting.
  * information about a winner of prizes donated by some of our sponsors/partners.
  * fulfillments of legal or regulatory disclosure requirements.

### YOUR CONSENT

By using the Freddie Awards, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

### CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, post in our voluntary communication newsletter and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on February 1, 2011

### CONTACTING US

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us:

**The Freddie Awards**  
1930 Frequent Flyer Point  
Colorado Springs, CO 80915  
Contact Us
